week 15 day 1 stuttering stutter communication disorder stuck have trouble genetic trauma
factor outgrow adulthood consistent tense anxious stay away from lead to day two
Isadora Duncan reputation alive and well stick to old-fashioned passionate expression gather
improvisation set lift day three what is beauty constantly consider come and go aspect symmetry
sign necessarily geography obsession fit value bound Renaissance forehead pluck day four danger
in the sea Gulf regulate seal drill absolutely strengthen blowout automatically gush gallon
livelihood decade day five the Rose City Canyon carve pass-through supplies prosperous admire
impressive rely on nickname abandoned tribe heritage day six capo era the dance of war
capa era descendant bind revolt battle rhythm stringed sweep cartwheel handstand acrobatic
opponent catch somebody off-guard fitness day seven yoga unity join broadly speaking
combination mental physical breathing pose flexibility challenging relief continent studio